STANDARD FOR LIFE
I'll just say yes You lead the way
I'm not afraid of what it means for me to say
This life You gave is not my own
I'm trusting You to hear my yes to lead me on
Yes Lord yes Lord my life is Yours
I'll just say yes You lead the way
I'm not afraid of what it means for me to say
This life You gave is not my own
I'm trusting You to hear my yes to lead me on
Yes Lord yes Lord my life is Yours
Hallelujah.
You have decreed the answer to yourself; give thanks to God for your confession.
That is strong confession.
Faith is expecting Jesus to do what He promised to do – that is favour.
He promised to favour you and you have decreed it already.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We want to fight – wage war aggressively against those things you want to do and you do not do.
You want to be faithful but you find yourself unfaithful.
Demons are the cause.
Many things you want to do but you do not do.
For you, you want to be faithful, kind, obedient but you find yourself otherwise – losing control.
Demons are the cause; demons are behind it.
Are you with me?
This is why we are here, to fight those demons aggressively, in the name of Jesus
and to restore you back because it takes control of your emotions.
You react emotionally.
Ordinarily, as a Christian, you would not react like that.
If I'm right...
It seems to take control of your emotions.
It has to lose that grip, in the name of Jesus; and leave you alone, because you are a child of God.
You are a child of God; that is why you are here today.
You know, ordinarily you can't come here.
Are you with me?
Ordinarily, you can't come here, going by what you have gone through before coming here.
What you have seen before coming here, what you have heard before coming here,
the pain and all you have gone through – ordinarily, you cannot come here.
This is to prove that you are a child of God.
Ordinarily, you would have been here a long time ago.
There are many people here today who were supposed to be here ten years ago;
ordinarily, they would have been here ten years ago.
But you can't come here ordinarily.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neighbour, "Ordinarily, you cannot come here".
[Ordinarily, you cannot come here.]
And ordinarily, you would not be able to obey what you hear today or what you are seeing;
ordinarily, you cannot obey them.
You can say you are not ordinary.
You are not ordinary; so, why do you compare yourself to others?
When others go this way, you want to go that way.
YOU ARE NOT LIKE OTHERS
When you are sick...
You always compare your sickness to others.
Your sickness is not like others.
Your sickness is not to kill you or destroy you but to strengthen your desire for God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neighbour, "I am not ordinary".
[I am not ordinary.]
If you know that your disappointment is not like others -
others, their disappointment is to destroy them, to ruin them.
But your disappointment is to strengthen your desire, to prepare you for a new life coming.
You need some...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neighbour, "I am not ordinary".
[I am not ordinary.]
If you know you are not ordinary, why do you compare yourself to others?
When others have headache, their headache can kill them – your headache cannot kill you.
It is the same name; headache, cancer, liver problem - but yours are not like others.
Your pain is not like others.
Are you with me?
Stop comparing yourself to others.
When others laugh you laugh - no.
You are under His eyes; you must hear from above.
You need corresponding power to do whatever you want to do.
They don't need any to do whatever they want to do.
You are not ordinary - tell you neighbour.
[You are not ordinary.]
Stop comparing yourself to others.
When others want to go this way you want to go that way.
This is why you are facing difficulties.
Your pain, from today, is not like others.
The Bible says that you will have pain, but that pain is not like the pain of others.
Your pain could be headache, setback, disappointment, even your pain could be divorce.
That divorce is not like others – it is to preserve you from something bad that is coming.
When you have some little problem you will look at others that had such a problem in the past.
You will see what happened to them; they die, they cripple;
you would think the same thing would happen to you - no.
Your problem is no like others.
God is aware of your pain.
He said, 'In this world, there will be trouble, tribulation; cheer up, I'm aware'.
Whatever you are going through now is for a purpose.
What are you going through?
Ask your neighbour.
[What are you going through?]
It is not possible for anyone to say, "I am not going through anything".
You must be going through something because you are a stranger in here.
You are a stranger.
If you are in a place where you are a stranger you cannot avoid being punched.
It is not possible when you find yourself as a stranger in a new city, new place...
You are a stranger, no matter how many years you spend on this earth.
You are a stranger and you are in the market.
No matter how many years you spend in the market, you will still return home.
Tell your neighbour, "No matter how many years you spend in the market, you will return home".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You will definitely return home.
What we are going through is not like others.
You must be going through something because there is no 'free zone'.
You must be going through something.
That does not mean you are not a Christian or a friend of Jesus.
That does not mean you are not a candidate of Heaven – you are a candidate.
You must be going through something.
That something is the purpose of your praying the more, fasting the more.
Ask your neighbour, "What are you going through?"
I cannot hear you.
[What are you going through?]
I cannot hear you
It is meant to strengthen you; tell you neighbour.
[It is meant to strengthen you]
It is meant to prepare you for eternal life.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That does not mean because you are going through something you will not say, "Thank You, Jesus".
You refuse to say "Thank You, Jesus".
You always ask for healing, deliverance... No.
If you are waiting for when you will be one hundred percent free,
you will not say, "Thank You, Jesus" one day.
That time will never come.
Tell your neighbour.
[That time will never come.]
Waiting for a hundred percent free – that time will never come.
Waiting for a hundred percent free – that time may never come.
I cannot hear you.
[Waiting for a hundred percent free – that time may never come.]
That is what you are waiting for.
Yesterday you had a headache.
Now the headache is gone.
Now stomachache.
Because of stomachache you will not give thanks to God for taking away the headache.
What you are waiting for is to be one hundred percent pain free and success in business.
Oh my God.
You can move freely.
You receive a phone call, "Hello, the business is fine".
You sleep well - no nightmares.
You open the doors - no problem.
Everybody praises you.
No one talks bad about you.
No one persecutes or intimidates you.
This is what you are waiting for.
That time may never come.
If the money in business comes, there will come a problem to consume this money.
Can you see?
When there is no money, your child has no sickness.
When there is money your child has a sickness.
When you do not have money nobody would call you a bad name.
When you have money they would say you did a ritual.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That time may never come because you are a stranger in the market.
A man may be sick in body and yet, a friend of God.
If you see somebody sick you say this is a result of a sin.
It is an enemy.
When you see somebody sick you say it is a result of a sin... No.
A man may be sick and yet, a favourite of Jesus.
Don’t let your situation rule you.
The situation used to talk, it has a voice.
You will hear; "Why this problem? Because you are not faithful. Because Jesus doesn't love you.
That is why you have this problem. Look at your colleague who is a smoker - a "club-goer;
his life is fine. You don't have money. He is the one giving you money."
This kind of voice is to overthrow your position.
Ordinarily, you cannot come here.
You wake up in the morning, you dress up; something would talk to you, "Don't go" - it is a battle.
"Don't go. What are you going to do there? The man will not come out. He will not see you."
You will receive a phone call, saying that million dollars has been reserved for you, you just have to come.
Oh, I will not go to the church...
But at the end - you are here.
YOU ARE NOT LIKE OTHERS
That is what I mean by "ordinarily, you cannot come here."
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If it is not in Spirit, it is not in truth – ordinarily, you cannot come here.
Tell your neighbour, "If it is not in Spirit, it is not in truth – ordinarily, you cannot come here. "
How do you know where you are going is a place where God wants you to be?
The moment you have the thought of going there, battle starts.
Trouble.
Maybe it is a place, where God wants you to be - and you receive a news that you must go there.
It may take two weeks to go.
The trouble will come.
Thoughts of not going there will come.
You may even be arrested in order to stop you from going there.
A lot of news, phone calls, troubles...
You may not even have money to come.
You may have an accident on the day of coming; nothing would happen to you, but the vehicle will be damaged.
Just to stop you from going there.
There are many businesses you have lost to prevent you from coming here.
Whatever you want to do and it’s smooth at the beginning, know the end is not good.
When you start something and the beginning is smooth, profitable; know that the end is to cry about.
Anything close to Jesus receives an attack.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You have lost many relationships because hearing that this man is a criminal; whereas satan doesn't want you
to continue this relationship.
It is a relationship that would be profitable and would change and transform your life.
But someone says that this man is a criminal.
They will even send a letter, a text message...
They will do a lot to stop you.
Many of you stopped a lot of relationships just because of what you had heard.
And that is the relationship that could have changed your life and career.
Are you talking of business?
When you start a business that would transform your life, take you to "high places", it would look like a trouble.
You will see lost in whatever you invest in.
As you move the troubles continue.
As you move the troubles continue to the extent you find yourself in debts.
Please continue; these troubles will stop somewhere.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Those troubles will stop somewhere and the beginning of your joy is there.
Many of you has today many business cards.
You don' know which one to use.
You were once a lawyer, now you are a contractor of any kind.
It is because of failures, debts you keep running from one business to another.
And you don't know that those things are a proof of genuineness of what you are doing.
Are you talking of marriage?
There are many marriages today...
My God.
People move from one man to another, one woman to another; just because of crisis -
and that crisis is a test to proof that this is a marriage from God.
There can be no genuine without first, fake.
When you meet a good family today; they will tell you what they have gone through,
before becoming a "role model".
A good marriage; when you meet them they will tell you what they have gone through.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In the same business...
Many businessman today that are at the centre of their own world - it was a sack letter that put them there.
The sack letter they received initially gave them that idea to start their own business.
Today, they are world generals.
But many of us, while receiving a sack letter, think of committing suicide, or joining a criminal gang.
Many are arm-robbers, murderers today.
When you catch them they will tell you, "I was once a manager of a company. I was sucked.
I had nothing to do. I joined the arm-robbers".
Whereas many successful businessmen started their own business when the sack letter was given them.
Life is just like that.
You need to sit down and ask yourself, "Am I right?"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In our walking with the Lord, there are good and hard times.
In our walking with the Lord; time to laugh and time to cry.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You know those things that can cause crying.
It could be persecution, sickness, pains of all kinds.
Failure, hatred, temptation.
In our walking with the Lord, there are good and hard times alike.
Write it down.
This is to walk together with Jesus.
There are good times and there are hard times, when we are walking.
You know good times, but hard times you may not know.
Good time is a time to laugh, "I am happy, everything is OK".
And there is a hard time, and you know those things that can cause crying.
You know those things.
What you are going through.
These are the things that can cause crying;
pain,
sickness - you may receive a medical report saying that, "this is death".
You would cry.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
But you never consider the other side
in your walking with Him.
This is why Himself said, "I pray your faith will not fail".
Because He knew that there would be hard times, time to cry.
You would rather seek a witch doctor than Jesus.
He said, "I pray your faith will not fail", when the hard time comes, while walking with me.
Tell your neighbour, "I pray your faith will not fail".
It means that something will challenge you, tempt you, hit you, bite you, curse you, something will... Oh my God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In a hard time, when you are overwhelmed, you lose relationship with Jesus.
At the same time you cannot...
The joyful heart is where Jesus...
When you are overwhelmed...
The thing that can make you cry, and overwhelms you - you cannot serve God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This is what happens to you people today.
You seem to be overwhelmed.
Things that can make you cry; not only you cry but you are overwhelmed by the thing.
Not only you cry, complain, murmur, you are despaired but you are overwhelmed.
When you are overwhelmed by the situation you cannot pray.
You will lose the relationship.
The relationship is gone.
Then you ask, "Why me of this?"
You begin to look at Jesus in a bad light.
Ordinarily, you cannot be here.
If you are overwhelmed by your situation you cannot come here.
You are here because your are not overwhelmed yet.
You have a situation but you are not overwhelmed yet.
You cannot come here ordinarily -
as it should be by divine will.
God is aware of your coming here.
[Amen.]
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today,
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons, and testimonies from SCOAN
Emmanuel TV; changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.